te-lists.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy for Te-Lists.com

##  Privacy Policy for Te-Lists.com

At Te-Lists.Com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by the site, how it is used and safeguard your information. 

###  Log Files 

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. 

###  Cookies and Web Beacons

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums. 

We also use third party advertisements on Te-Lists.com to support our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site which will also send these advertisers information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited. 

###  DoubleClick DART cookies 

We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests ("interest based targeting"). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses "non personally identifiable information". It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx 

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. 

This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts 

###  Email Address 

We collect the e-mail addresses of visitors those who post ads to our site. We are not sharing any of those email addresses to any third party. 

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at [support@telists.com](mailto:support@telists.com)
